}Welcome to this exceptional live/work residence.
}Step inside this sprawling 3,500 sq. ft. bungalow.
}Feel the warmth of elevated living throughout.
}Five spacious bedrooms invite relaxation and comfort.
}Each bedroom offers unique charm and flexibility.
}Four well-appointed bathrooms ensure convenience for everyone.
}Picture gatherings in the expansive open living area.
}The chef&apos;s kitchen is a dream come true.
}Imagine cooking on gorgeous marble countertops.
}Natural light cascades through every corner here.
}The heated workshop is a creative haven.
}Perfect for projects or hobbies you love.
}Two separate driveways offer incredible accessibility.
}Direct access to the rear yard enhances privacy.
}Just a minute from Highway 401’s convenience.
}Future industrial zoning potential adds remarkable value.
}This home is truly a rare find.
}Imagine the possibilities this space holds.
}Thank you for joining this special tour.
}We hope you feel at home here.