}Welcome to this incredible opportunity!
}Imagine the possibilities on this prime lot.
}A rare permit-issued individual building lot awaits you.
}Picture a stunning home on this 25 by 125 space.
}The city has already approved severance.
}With a city-assigned address, your dreams can begin.
}Think of all the designs you can create here.
}Whether you&apos;re a builder or an investor, this is gold.
}Envision a vibrant community blossoming around you.
}Just steps away from local amenities and parks.
}The potential here is truly limitless.
}Don&apos;t miss your chance to seize this opportunity.
}Imagine your vision coming to life in this lot.
}Thank you for exploring this unique chance with us!
}We can&apos;t wait to see what you create here.