}Welcome to this stunning estate in the exclusive Rattray Marsh enclave.
}As you step inside, the grand foyer greets you with coffered ceilings.
}Notice the sweeping staircase that invites you further into luxury.
}Every corner showcases intricate wainscotting and custom millwork throughout.
}The chef&apos;s kitchen is truly a culinary dream with high-end appliances.
}Gather around the oversized island, perfect for family and friends.
}Flowing into the family room, feel the warmth from the gas fireplace.
}With 20-foot ceilings, this space feels both expansive and inviting.
}Gaze through the windows to the indoor swimming pool that&apos;s a showstopper.
}The pool area is an entertainer&apos;s paradise, complete with a wet bar.
}Ascend to the Owners Suite, your private retreat with a lovely balcony.
}Each additional bedroom boasts its own stylish ensuite and walk-in closet.
}The lower level offers endless entertainment options for you and your guests.
}Thank you for touring this exquisite home, where luxury meets lifestyle.