}Welcome to this unique opportunity!
}Imagine your dream home right here.
}A rare, permit-issued building lot awaits.
}Picture a stunning modern design coming to life.
}This lot measures twenty-five by one hundred twenty-five feet.
}Envision the possibilities for your vision.
}Severance is already approved, how exciting!
}The city has assigned a unique address.
}A building permit is in hand, ready for you.
}Investors and builders will see great potential.
}Create a masterpiece that stands out.
}This is more than just land; it&apos;s a canvas.
}A chance to craft a contemporary haven.
}Picture yourself in a vibrant new community.
}The possibilities are endless on this lot.
}Imagine the joy of designing your own space.
}Thank you for exploring this opportunity with me!
}I can&apos;t wait to see your vision unfold.