}Welcome to this luxurious estate in Rattray Marsh, Mississauga.
}As you step inside, a grand foyer greets you with elegance.
}Look at that sweeping staircase and stunning coffered ceilings.
}The living spaces are expansive, featuring custom millwork and wainscotting.
}Imagine cooking in this chef&apos;s kitchen with high-end appliances.
}Gather around the oversized island, perfect for family and friends.
}The family room showcases a floor-to-ceiling gas fireplace, truly breathtaking.
}Step into the indoor swimming pool area, designed for year-round fun.
}Ascend to the Owners Suite, a private retreat with a luxurious ensuite.
}Thank you for joining me on this remarkable tour; your dream home awaits!