}Welcome to this unique opportunity.
}Imagine building your dream home here.
}This rare lot is waiting for you.
}A generous 25 by 125 feet of potential.
}Perfect for builders and investors alike.
}Severance approved, ready for your vision.
}Picture a stunning modern design emerging.
}Contemporary architecture by renowned Contempo Studios.
}Over 2,100 square feet of luxury awaits.
}Envision your life unfolding in this space.
}With a basement, it’s over 2,950 square feet.
}All architectural drawings are ready for you.
}Visualize hosting friends in your new home.
}Imagine the possibilities of this blank canvas.
}This is more than just a lot.
}It’s the start of your new journey.
}Thank you for exploring this opportunity!